[{"id":10,"question":"Which of the following is a command in Linux?","description":null,"answers":{"answer_a":"w","answer_b":"x","answer_c":"t","answer_d":"All of the Above","answer_e":null,"answer_f":null},"multiple_correct_answers":"false","correct_answers":{"answer_a_correct":"true","answer_b_correct":"false","answer_c_correct":"false","answer_d_correct":"false","answer_e_correct":"false","answer_f_correct":"false"},"correct_answer":"answer_a","explanation":null,"tip":null,"tags":[{"name":"Linux"}],"category":"Linux","difficulty":"Easy"},{"id":716,"question":"An abstraction in kubernetes which defines a logical set of pods and a policy to access them.","description":null,"answers":{"answer_a":"node","answer_b":"cluster","answer_c":"service","answer_d":"set","answer_e":null,"answer_f":null},"multiple_correct_answers":"true","correct_answers":{"answer_a_correct":"false","answer_b_correct":"false","answer_c_correct":"true","answer_d_correct":"false","answer_e_correct":"false","answer_f_correct":"false"},"correct_answer":"answer_a","explanation":"A service is a grouping of pods that are running on the cluster. Services are \"cheap\" and you can have many services within the cluster.","tip":null,"tags":[{"name":"Kubernetes"}],"category":"Linux","difficulty":"Easy"},{"id":223,"question":"Which keyword is used with the UPDATE command to change the value?","description":null,"answers":{"answer_a":"CHANGE","answer_b":"MODIFY","answer_c":"ADD","answer_d":"SET","answer_e":null,"answer_f":null},"multiple_correct_answers":"false","correct_answers":{"answer_a_correct":"false","answer_b_correct":"false","answer_c_correct":"false","answer_d_correct":"true","answer_e_correct":"false","answer_f_correct":"false"},"correct_answer":"answer_a","explanation":null,"tip":null,"tags":[{"name":"MySQL"}],"category":"Linux","difficulty":"Easy"},{"id":49,"question":"Which of the following key combinations allows to terminate the current process in Linux shell?","description":null,"answers":{"answer_a":"Ctrl + C","answer_b":"Ctrl + Z","answer_c":"Ctrl + A","answer_d":"Ctrl + L","answer_e":null,"answer_f":null},"multiple_correct_answers":"false","correct_answers":{"answer_a_correct":"true","answer_b_correct":"false","answer_c_correct":"false","answer_d_correct":"false","answer_e_correct":"false","answer_f_correct":"false"},"correct_answer":"answer_a","explanation":null,"tip":null,"tags":[{"name":"Linux"}],"category":"Linux","difficulty":"Easy"},{"id":654,"question":"Which option can be used with \u2018rm\u2019 command to prompt for file removal?","description":null,"answers":{"answer_a":"-ask","answer_b":"-i","answer_c":"-c","answer_d":"-n","answer_e":null,"answer_f":null},"multiple_correct_answers":"false","correct_answers":{"answer_a_correct":"false","answer_b_correct":"true","answer_c_correct":"false","answer_d_correct":"false","answer_e_correct":"false","answer_f_correct":"false"},"correct_answer":"answer_a","explanation":null,"tip":null,"tags":[{"name":"BASH"}],"category":"Linux","difficulty":"Easy"},{"id":647,"question":"Which command can be used to count characters in a text file?","description":null,"answers":{"answer_a":"ccount","answer_b":"fsize","answer_c":"count","answer_d":"wc","answer_e":null,"answer_f":null},"multiple_correct_answers":"false","correct_answers":{"answer_a_correct":"false","answer_b_correct":"true","answer_c_correct":"false","answer_d_correct":"false","answer_e_correct":"false","answer_f_correct":"false"},"correct_answer":"answer_a","explanation":null,"tip":null,"tags":[{"name":"BASH"}],"category":"Linux","difficulty":"Easy"},{"id":670,"question":"Which is the invalid file name in UNIX?","description":null,"answers":{"answer_a":"LINUX","answer_b":"a.widows","answer_c":"bill .gates","answer_d":"All of the above","answer_e":"None of the above","answer_f":null},"multiple_correct_answers":"false","correct_answers":{"answer_a_correct":"false","answer_b_correct":"false","answer_c_correct":"false","answer_d_correct":"false","answer_e_correct":"true","answer_f_correct":"false"},"correct_answer":"answer_a","explanation":null,"tip":null,"tags":[{"name":"BASH"}],"category":"Linux","difficulty":"Easy"},{"id":750,"question":"What is Minikube","description":null,"answers":{"answer_a":"Specification of a Kubernetes API object in JSON or YAML format","answer_b":"A pod object that a kubelet uses to represent a static pod","answer_c":"A tool for running Kubernetes locally","answer_d":"An abstraction used by Kubernetes to support multiple virtual clusters on the same physical cluster","answer_e":null,"answer_f":null},"multiple_correct_answers":"false","correct_answers":{"answer_a_correct":"false","answer_b_correct":"false","answer_c_correct":"true","answer_d_correct":"false","answer_e_correct":"false","answer_f_correct":"false"},"correct_answer":"answer_a","explanation":null,"tip":null,"tags":[{"name":"Kubernetes"}],"category":"Linux","difficulty":"Easy"},{"id":527,"question":"HTML supports","description":null,"answers":{"answer_a":"ordered lists","answer_b":"unordered lists","answer_c":"both type of lists","answer_d":"does not support those types","answer_e":null,"answer_f":null},"multiple_correct_answers":"false","correct_answers":{"answer_a_correct":"false","answer_b_correct":"false","answer_c_correct":"true","answer_d_correct":"false","answer_e_correct":"false","answer_f_correct":"false"},"correct_answer":"answer_a","explanation":null,"tip":null,"tags":[{"name":"HTML"}],"category":"Linux","difficulty":"Easy"},{"id":656,"question":"Which filter can be applied on lines of text for arranging in ascending or descending order?","description":null,"answers":{"answer_a":"sort","answer_b":"arrange","answer_c":"collate","answer_d":"None of the above","answer_e":null,"answer_f":null},"multiple_correct_answers":"false","correct_answers":{"answer_a_correct":"true","answer_b_correct":"false","answer_c_correct":"false","answer_d_correct":"false","answer_e_correct":"false","answer_f_correct":"false"},"correct_answer":"answer_a","explanation":null,"tip":null,"tags":[{"name":"BASH"}],"category":"Linux","difficulty":"Easy"}]